Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series XI is arranged in 4 sub-series by Union file number.
Series XII is arranged in 8 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series XI. BILLS
  - Sub-Series 208-0. Bills
    - General, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 53)
      Jan. 1, 1967-Sept. 25, 1967.
  - Sub-Series 208-4. Bills
    - Furniture and Equipment, 1960-1962 (Box 49, Folder 54)
      1960-Dec. 31, 1962.
  - Sub-Series 208-6. Bills
    - Operating Expense. Dodge A-100 Camper to Harry W. Camper, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 55)
      1966 April 23
  - Sub-Series 208-6. Bills
    - Operating Expense. Dodge A-100 Camper to H. L. Tuttle, 1964 (Box 49, Folder 56)
      Nov. 1, 1964.
- Series XII. STATE FEDERATIONS OF LABOR
  - Sub-Series 211-0. State Federations of Labor
    - General, 1960-1962 (Box 49a, Folder 1)
    - General, 1957-1959 (Box 49a, Folder 2)
      October 1957-59.
  - Sub-Series 211-4. State Federations of Labor
    - California State Federation of Labor, 1939-1961 (Box 49a, Folder 3)
      1939-Dec. 31, 1961.
  - Sub-Series 211-11. State Federations of Labor
    - Illinois State Federation of Labor, 1950-1960 (Box 49a, Folder 4)
      1950-Dec. 31, 1960.
  - Sub-Series 211-13. State Federations of Labor
    - Iowa State Federation of Labor, 1959-1963 (Box 49a, Folder 5)
      1959-Dec. 31, 1963.
  - Sub-Series 211-14. State Federations of Labor
    - Kansas State Federation of Labor, 1959-1963 (Box 49a, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 211-16. State Federations of Labor
    - Louisiana State Federation of Labor, 1922-1957 (Box 49a, Folder 7)
      1922-Dec. 31, 1957.
  - Sub-Series 211-31. State Federations of Labor
    - New York State Federation of Labor, 1924-1959 (Box 49a, Folder 8)
      1924-Dec. 31, 1959.
  - Sub-Series 211-34. State Federations of Labor
    - Ohio State Federation of Labor, 1930-1960 (Box 49a, Folder 9)
      1930-Dec. 31, 1960.